[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food do Tasmanian devils prefer in the wild?", "correct_answer": "Carrion", "incorrect_answers": ["Sheep", "Insects", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which city was Albert Einstein born ?", "correct_answer": "Ulm", "incorrect_answers": ["Berlin", "Bonn", "Munich"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main difference between fungi and plants when cell structure is considered?", "correct_answer": "Fungi do not have cellulose in their cell walls", "incorrect_answers": ["Fungal cells contain membrane-bound nuclei", "Fungi lack ribosomes", "Fungi lack mitochodria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elizabeth Berkley starred in this movie with Campbell Scott, Jesse Eisenberg and Isabella Rosselini.", "correct_answer": "Roger Dodger", "incorrect_answers": ["Mrs. Parker and the Vicious Circle", "Death Becomes Her", "Showgirls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year is the movie Appaloosa set?", "correct_answer": "1882", "incorrect_answers": ["1885", "1865", "1901"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What distinction does Sir Timothy Berners-Lee hold?", "correct_answer": "He is the inventor of the World Wide Web.", "incorrect_answers": ["He was the first RAF pilot to shoot down a plane.", "He made  the first cell phone call.", "He was the first non-American to hold a US patent."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many groups are the twelve signs arranged in?", "correct_answer": "4 groups of 3", "incorrect_answers": ["3 groups of 4", "2 groups of 6", "1 groups of 12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the movie Mirrors with Kiefer Sutherland released?", "correct_answer": "2008", "incorrect_answers": ["2001", "2007", "2005"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the first stick antiperspirant patented?", "correct_answer": "1888", "incorrect_answers": ["1942", "1919", "1951"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of mammal is the kangaroo?", "correct_answer": "Marsupial", "incorrect_answers": ["Monotreme", "All of these", "Amniote"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The milk of which of these mammals is used for consumption by humans?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Moose", "Reindeer", "Water buffalo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The symbols of this month are the sapphire and the forget-me-not.", "correct_answer": "September", "incorrect_answers": ["July", "February", "December"]}]